我要养五个孩子  都没错过上周这集
Jesus, I'm raising five kids, and I didn't miss last week.
你有什么借口
What's your excuse?
卡尔
Carl!
我试过给你搞药了  但小维给药柜上了锁
I tried to get your drugs, but v has her cabinet locked up,
她现在要收钱才肯给我
and she's making me buy them now.
我也许找到新肝了  真的吗  哪里找到的
I may have found a liver. Really? Where?
你的大姐  萨咪
Your older sister Sammi.
肝脏移植  弗兰克
A transplant? Oh, Frank.
我想把肝脏给你
I want to give you my liver.
-真的吗  -你还好吗
- Really? - You okay?
不怎么样  就是...
I could be better. You know, it's, um--
-不适应吗  -对  不适应
- Different? - Different, yeah.
加拉格一家在向上爬
The Gallaghers moving up the food chain.
那你俩打算什么时候做
So when do you plan on doing it?
-我要怎么开始  -突然
- How do I start? - Bam--
你就脱掉裤子  然后就搔首弄姿
You drop trou and expos-ay some sex-ay.
我这样会勾起你的性致吗
Does this make you cray?
今晚我邀请我哥跟我们一起吃晚餐
So I invited my brother out to dinner with us tonight.
这儿有单一麦芽威士忌
They have single-malt flights.
不不  今晚不喝
Oh, no, no, no, no. Not tonight.
喝吧  让我通过你间接感受下
Get it, so I can drink vicariously through you.
起来
Here we go.
-就快到了  兄弟  -好嘞
- Almost there, brother. - Okay.
-就在你右腿旁边  -好
- Right by your right leg, okay? - Okay. Yeah.
我永远不会告诉他的
I'm not telling him, ever.
-这事根本没发生过  -实实在在发生了呢
- This did not happen. - Oh, yes, it did.
而且它会再次发生  上瘾了
And it's gonna happen again, addict.
无耻家庭
第四季第四集
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：  爱卿遛小鸟   重案组李Sir   企鹅三星带花
■
翻译：  姚小事   拉图   Greentie
时间轴：  浓子   芝麻圆子
■
校对： Greentie   爱卿遛小鸟
后期： IcyLisle          总监： 落
■
你昨晚让人在轻轨上用手指操了你
You let some dude finger you last night on the EL?
被你说得好肮脏  而且也不是随便哪个人
You make it sound so filthy. And he's not just any dude.
没错  是你男朋友的哥哥
No, he's your boyfriend's brother.
我知道
I know.
-你老板的哥哥  -我知道
- Your boss's brother. - I know, okay?
-我没法解释  -我可以
- I can't explain it. - I can.
还记得肖恩吗  在卡尔面前嗑药的那个
Remember Shawn? Did speedballs in front of Carl?
你跟他处了多久  五个月
You stayed with him for what, five months?
然后是杰森  对吧
And then it was Jason, right?
有愤怒管理问题的杰森
Jason with the anger issues--
如果拿刀砍在餐厅插队的人
I mean, if you consider stabbing a guy for jumping the line
-算"问题"的话  -我知道了
- at the cracker barrel an issue. - Yeah, I get it.
接着又是说谎精人夫偷车贼吉米·史蒂夫
And then there was Jimmy Steve the lying, married car thief.
菲  这份工作对你是件好事
Fi, this job is a good thing for you.
只是个错误而已  已经过去了
It was a mistake, okay? It's--it's over.
最好是
It better be.
我可没空整天给你人生建议
I can't be over here Dr. Phil-ing your ass.
-我要去酒吧了  -这么早
- I got to go to the Alibi. - This early?
是啊  这样小凯就不用付凯特加班费了
Yeah, it saves Kev from having to pay Kate overtime.
他还担心孩子的事吗
Is he still freaking out about the babies?
还有酒吧的事
And the bar.
工薪税下周就要交了
Payroll taxes are due next week.
营业执照要续期  设施要更新
Business license has to be renewed, utilities.
有人看到我的唇彩吗
Has anyone seen my lip gloss?
你好啊  小黛
Well, hi, Debs.
-卡尔  -干嘛
- Carl! - What?
你应该给利亚姆做早餐的
You're supposed to make Liam breakfast.
-又不是我的活  -就是你的
- It's not my job. - It is your job.
别吵了
Relax, relax.
给你  比化妆品有营养多了
Here, more nutritious than makeup.
我昨天做了一笔大买卖  卖出了一万个杯子
I made a big sale yesterday, 10,000 units.
"恭喜  菲奥娜"
"Congrats, Fiona."
"干得好  我们真为你骄傲"
"Great job. We're so proud of you."
干嘛
What?
他还是不要跟你说话  午餐钱
He's still not talking to you. Lunch.
我以前可是你们的姐姐  不仅是自动取款机
You know, I used to be your sister, not just an ATM.
我喜欢这件上衣  你看起来很可爱
I like that top. You look cute.
我才不想要可爱
I'm not trying to look cute.
我今天可以送你去学校
I could walk you to school today.
我又不是一年级
I'm not in the first grade!
我们最近很少聊天
We just haven't talked that much lately,
算是我的错吧
and maybe that's my fault.
我经常不着家
I haven't been around as much.
你不是要去上班的吗
Yeah, well, don't you have to get to work?
迟一点没关系
I can be late.
你正在经历的事  我都经历过
Whatever you're going through, guess what--I did too.
你有大把时间长大
You got plenty of time to grow up.
现在带点孩子气挺好的
It's okay to just be a kid.
大脑里的血液都跑到下面的小脑袋里了
Careful you don't pass out, with all the blood rushing
你可小心别昏过去了
from your big head to your little head.
我开始好奇什么时候能让你的"马达"动起来了
I was beginning to wonder when I'd get your motor revving.
我去看看他们准备好了没
Okay, I'm gonna go see if they're ready yet.
什么时候能在我身上动刀
How soon do I go under the knife?
移植  什么时候能做
The transplant--how soon?
假设捐献人能通过交叉配血
Uh, assuming your donor passes the cross-match
以及口服葡萄糖胺测试  那...
And oral glucosamine tests without issue, then--
她能通过  她是我女儿
She'll pass. She's my daughter.
那从医学角度来说
Oh, well, then we'll have everything we need
就万事俱备了
from a medical standpoint.
什么意思
W-what does that mean?
你没有医保
You don't have health insurance.
所以才要急诊室啊
That's what the E.R. is for.
急诊室不做器官移植手术
They don't do transplants in the E.R.
我们得把你排在候补名单上
We're gonna have to put you on a wait list
等待无偿做器官移植手术的医生
with one of the few doctors who perform transplants pro bono.
不幸的是  这名单很长
Unfortunately, that list is pretty long.
-要等几周  -要以年计
- Weeks? - More like years.
-年  -几年吧  除非情况危急
- Years? - A couple, unless it's dire.
危急  我快死了
Dire? Well, um, I'm dying.
候补名单上其他几千人也是这样
So are the thousands of others on the pro bono list.
要多少
How much?
如果我自付手术费  要多少钱
If I paid for the operation myself, how much?
器官移植手术极其复杂
Transplant surgery is a very complicated procedure
涵盖至少十二名专科医生
involving more than a dozen specialties
以及医院里各个部门
and many different departments of the hospital.
需要全院调整
Okay, it's a shakedown.
我们美好的医保系统很有用
Our glorious health-care system at work.
要多少
How much?
总费用在十五万吧  上下相差一万左右
All in, 150 grand, give or take $10,000.
准备好啦  测试四点就能结束
Ready. The tests will be done by 4:00.
过来接我  然后我们去庆祝
Come get me, and we'll celebrate.
我和女儿感情很好
My daughter and I are very close.
-一杯三块  -几时开始的
- 3 bucks a shot. - Since when?
你们要生一窝娃又不怪我们
It ain't our fault you got a herd of kids on the way.
斯坦从不打理楼上的石棉也不怪我们
Yeah, and it's not our fault that stan never took care
不过猜猜谁要为此买单
of the asbestos upstairs, but guess who has to pay for it.
石棉怎么了  我家屋顶上一大堆
Asbestos isn't so bad. I got lots of it
看我还活得好好的啊
in the ceiling at my house, and look at me.
跟市政局的人说去
Tell that to the city.
要是我们不清理掉那些东西  他们就要我们停业
If we don't get it removed, they're gonna shut us down.
清洁公司开价六千块
The removal company wants 6 grand.
怎么不去抢
Might as well be $6 million.
该死的护士助手一副
Fucking candy striper giving me a look
看变态的眼神看我
like I'm a fucking degenerate.
埃及皇室  印加人  甚至亚瑟王
Egyptian royals, the Incas, hell, King Arthur,
都是家族内部联姻的
they all kept it in the family.
要不是俄狄浦斯
We probably still would
毁了一切  也许我们现在还是这样
if Oedipus hadn't ruined it for all of us.
来吧  随便抨击  但让我先问个问题
So, fine, cast the first stone. But let me ask you--
如果我们都是亚当和夏娃的孩子
If we all came from just Adam and Eve in the beginning...
你们说吧
Well, you do the math!
弗兰克  废话能说得
Frank, can you please keep the nonsense rambling
小声点吗
down to a minimum?
这儿还有人真有问题要解决呢
Some of us have problems that we're trying to figure out.
等你为了活命需要十五万时
When you need 150 grand just to live,
咱们再来谈"问题"
we'll talk about problems.
你可以把房子烧了来骗保
You could burn your house down for the insurance money.
我叔叔多里斯就这么干过
That's what my uncle Doris did.
是啊  他差点把整个社区都烧了
Yeah, and he almost burned down the entire neighborhood.
加太多助燃剂了
Too much accelerant.
但他们没找到确凿证据
But they never got the charges to stick.
纵火
Jewish lightning--
真是犹太同胞
the most inspired
对这个社会最大的贡献
of our Hebrew brethren's contribution to society.
那房子又不是你的
You don't even own the damn house.
那希拉的房子呢
What about Sheila's house?
你可以跟她分成
You could split the dough with her.
-她买保险了吗  -买了
- She got insurance? - Yeah.
我找埃迪医嘱的时候看到过保单
Yeah, I saw the policy when I was looking for eddie's will.
弗兰克  你要在这儿抽大麻的话
You know, Frank, if you're gonna smoke that in here,
至少让我来一口吧
at least give me a hit.
-她不会答应的  -慢着
- She's never gonna go for it. - Well, wait, wait.
谁说我们要告诉她了
Who says we have to tell her?
弗兰克  你不能烧毁那位好心女士的家
Frank, you are not gonna burn down that nice woman's house.
不  不是烧毁
No, not burn down.
她有责任险
She's got liability.
来一场大事故  就能拿到保险金了
One big accident, and her insurance has to pay up.
-二元论  -笛卡尔
- Cartesian dualism. - Descartes.
-绝对...  -命令  康德
- Categorical- - Imperative. Kant.
这次考试我们妥妥能拿下
We're gonna ace this test, bro.
收工
All right.
我们得走了  你准备好了吗
We got to jet. You ready to go?
还没  我得去烘干机里拿裤子
No, I got to grab my pants out of the dryer.
-现在吗  -是的
- Right now? - Yeah.
-我马上就来  -好的
- I'll be right behind you. - All right.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
搞什么
What the fuck?
你
Yo!
至少得给我留点硬币吧  操
Did you at least leave me some quarters? Fuck.
朗
Ron!
在吗  希拉
Hey, Sheila!
希拉
Sheila!
操  你妈逼的  操
Cocksuck-- fuck, motherfuck, fuck.
我知道  对不起  我晚了几分钟
Yeah, I know. Sorry. I'm a few minutes late.
六分钟
Six minutes.
我知道  我只是
Yeah, I know. I just--
被锁在寝室外面了  好吗
I got locked out of my dorm room, right?
有个女的  她把我的衣服
'Cause--'cause this chick, she pulled my laundry
从烘干机里拿出来了  我
out of the dryer early, and my--
我牛仔裤还是湿的
My jeans are still wet. Um...
错过的时间就算了
Look, I'm not asking for the time I missed,
还剩多久我就答多久
just the time I have left.
-这样不行  -为什么
- It doesn't work that way. - Why not?
我不会跟你辩论这件事
I'm not going to argue about this.
为了这个考试我复习了好久  好吗
Look, I studied my ass off for this test, okay?
让我进去吧  我会向你证明的
Just let me in, and I will prove it to you.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
别这么混蛋  赶紧让我考试吧
Don't be a fucking prick. Just let me take the damn test.
这他妈是怎么回事
What the fuck is this?
昨天你给人口交了几次
How many blow jobs you give yesterday?
-十次  -打了几次手枪
- Ten blow jobs. - How many tugs?
-五次  -此外还有两个男的
- Five. - That's on top of two guys
要了全套骑乘式服务
who shelled out for a full belly ride.
你就用两百块打发她走吗
You send her home with a measly 200 bucks?
萨莎定的价
Sasha sets the price.
萨莎得认识到
Well, Sasha needs to find out
我老婆是妓女  不是奴隶
that my wife's a hooker, not a slave.
好了  好了  来真的了
Okay. Okay. Now this is happening.
出来  快出来
Out! Get out!
走  对的
Let's go! Yes.
穿上  走人
Put it on, and let's go. Hey!
来吧  你们不该被这么对待
Come on, you deserve better than this.
不管你是不是快高潮了  跟我走
I don't care if you're mid-pump. Come with me.
把陌生人的老二放嘴里的时候
Hey, you want to get paid a little more
你想不想多赚点钱
for putting a stranger's dick in your mouth?
跟我走  女士们
Come on, ladies.
快点  快点
Move, move.
晚点再清理吧
You can clean it off later.
我不管黏不黏  动起来
I don't care if it's sticky. Go!
快点  快点  出去
Come on. Come on, get out.
赶紧走  对的  穿上
Let's fucking go! Yes, let's-- yes, put that on.
妈的  大家好
Fuck me. Hi, guys.
走吧
Let's go!
看看你们的客户多满意
Look at all your happy customers, huh?
不给她们工钱谁也别想上床
No one's getting laid till they get paid.
我会告诉萨莎
I tell Sasha.
告诉他去他妈的
Yeah, tell him to go fuck himself.
你逗我吗  这顶多就算个扭伤
Are you kidding me? This is barely a sprain.
好像你学过医似的
Oh, like you've got a medical degree.
我处理个人责任险索赔很有经验
Hey, I handled enough personal liability claims
知道六位数的赔偿该伤成什么样
to know what a six-figure payout looks like.
你这个顶多两千
This is 2 grand, tops.
我需要十五万
I need 150.
那你最好带条断腿来见我
Well, then you better bring me a mangled femur,
或者  瞎一只眼
you know, or lose an eye.
瞎两只就更好了
Better yet, lose both eyes.
你一进屋  两个黑洞
You know, you walk in, empty sockets,
事情就成了
we got us a winner.
-天呐  弗兰克  -怎么了
- Jesus, Frank. - What?
要命了  抱歉
Jesus. I'm sorry.
有时候就这样
It does this sometimes.
你能不能  赶紧出去
Ugh, would you just-- go on, get out.
医院至少要预交五万美元
The hospital needs at least 50,000 down
他们才会安排手术
before they'll even schedule the operation.
他们接受预交
They take down payments?
你不把剩下的钱补上医院能怎么样
And what are they gonna do if you don't pay up the rest--
-驳回你的肝脏吗  -罗  没有钱我会死
- repo the liver? - Lou, I'm dead without this.
五万美元  我估计你需要
50 grand? Okay, we're talking, like,
部分残疾  身体至少百分之三十烧伤
partial paralysis, burns over at least 30% of your body.
如果你没胆子弄残自己
Hey, if you don't have the stones to hobble yourself,
那就找人帮你
find someone who'll do it for you.
你就是我要找的人
You're just the man I'm looking for.
-你怎么了  -我需要你帮忙
- What happened to you? - I need your help.
我拿锤子砸了小维的药柜  偷了些药
I took a hammer to V's stash, stole some pills.
在楼上
They're upstairs.
不不  在楼上吗
No, no, no, not tha-- they're upstairs?
待会再去拿
I'll--I'll get 'em later.
我要你弄断我的腿
I want you to break my leg.
我需要保险金
I need--I need the insurance money.
只有这样  我才能做移植手术
It's the only way I'll be able to pay for the transplant.
你要我伤害你
You want me to hurt you?
性命攸关
It's life or death.
如果你爱我  儿子  你会帮我
If you love me, son, you'll do this.
能拍下来挂到网上吗
Can I put it on YouTube?
当然...
Su--
不行
No.
-只欠一推  -头先着地怎么办
- Just one push. - What if I land on my head?
把你的腿伸进轨道  让火车压过去
Just stick your leg over the track and let it get run over.
放在外轨上行不行
What about the third rail?
什么是外轨
What's a third rail?
该死的奥巴马医保法案
Fucking Obamacare.
这是什么破体制
What kind of a system do we live in,
你得弄残自己才能活命
you have to cripple yourself to stay alive?
我可以用大锤砸你
I could get the sledgehammer.
不  不用了
No, that's all right.
-基瑟迪恩夫人有个电锯  -不用了
- Mrs. Jesudian has a table saw. - Forget it.
我的小药片呢
Where are those perc-me-ups?
你说性命攸关  小凯有台旧除草机
You said life or death. Kev has an old lawn mower.
可以从你脚上碾过去
Could run over your foot.
你是个好少年  儿子  药在哪
You're a good man, son. The pills?
床底下
Under the bed.
是的  马蒂和我
So, yeah, Matty and I spent
一整晚都  抱在一起
the whole night like that, spooning.
你看见比利·弗格斯了吗  艾丽说他在这儿
You see Billy Fergus? Ellie said he was here.
挺甜蜜的  他给我做了早餐
It was really sweet. He made me breakfast.
进入高潮再叫醒我
Wake me up when you get to the good part.
你用洗手液清洗"菜地"了吗
You clean out your cabbage patch with purell afterwards?
什么
What?
你就不会意外怀孕了
It keeps you from getting knocked up.
会让小游泳健将们醉晕
It gets the little swimmers so drunk,
它们就找不到卵子了
they can't find the egg.
没有
Um, no.
我们没有做爱  马蒂说我们应该...
Well, sex--we didn't have it. Matt said that we should--
你的星冰乐  霍莉
I got your frappuccino, Holly.
不是焦糖口味你就惨了
It better be caramel.
好了  走吧
Okay, go.
他是谁
Who's that?
山姆  赛斯  管他是谁
Sam? Seth? Who cares?
我让他做什么他就做什么
I tell him what to do, and he does it.
为什么
Why?
他认为我会在厕所里跟他"速战"一下
He thinks I'll maybe give him a quickie in the bathroom.
他能靠近我就够幸运的了
He's lucky I let him be seen near me.
比利在那  我看起来怎么样
There's Billy. How do I look?
-骚得很  -谢谢
- Slutty. - Thanks.
等等  霍莉
Um, wait. Holly?
马蒂说时机不对  这是坏事吗
Is it bad that Matty said it wasn't the right time?
他说的  "时机不对"
He said that? "It's not the right time"?
他是什么意思
What does it mean?
不知道  没有男孩这么跟我说过
I don't know. I've never had a guy say that.
我知道我跟你保证过
Yeah, I know I promised it to you.
我会把钱给你
Look, I'm gonna get you your money.
酒商吗
Liquor distributor?
不  是斯坦的儿子
No, it's Stan's son,
管我要他每月的五百美元
asking for his monthly $500
这钱我没有  因为这个破酒吧处于"盈利"
that I don't have for a bar that's in the black...
或是"亏损"状态  反正就快玩儿完了
or the red or whatever one it is where you're totally fucked.
你能不能付我点钱
Are you gonna pay for something else?
-你想让我喝醉吗  -你已经醉了
- Mm, trying to get me drunk? - You're already drunk.
我要付账单  你也付点钱吧
I got bills. Pay for something.
拿出好酒欢迎口交婊们
Hey, line up a shot for the Abe Lincoln of mouth-whores.
你说什么
Excuse me?
我解放了我老婆和她的吞精同僚
I emancipated my wife and her fellow cum guzzlers.
我要以其人之道
I'm gonna do to the Russians
还治俄国佬之身
what they've been doing to my girls,
-让他们也跪下来  -为什么
- bring them to their knees. - Why?
要不是那帮俄国佬把你老婆
Your wife wouldn't even be in this country
偷渡过来  她怎么会在这儿
if the russians hadn't smuggled her in originally.
所以他们就可以剥削她吗
That gives them the right to pay her next to nothing, huh?
我们渴了
We're thirsty.
还好厕所有水池
Good thing there's a sink in the fucking bathroom, huh?
俄国佬凭什么压榨她们
How do they get away with it?
什么凭什么
Get away with what?
逼她们贱卖自己
Forcing them to work for so cheap?
武力恐吓加上殴打吧
Guns and beatings mostly.
瞧瞧她们  哪里还有得选
I mean, look, what choice do they have?
她们一没身份证  二来不会说英语
They got no I.D. They barely speak the language.
初来乍到
They're fresh off the boat.
萨莎想付多少就付多少
Sasha can pay them whatever the fuck he wants.
但现在不同了  现在她们有了我
Not anymore. Now they got me.
-我马上回来  -你要去哪
- I'll be right back. - Where are you going?
美国家居连锁店
我去家得宝买些东西
I'm gonna pick something up from Home Depot.
现在吗
Now?
萨莎想见你一面
Sasha wants a meeting.
是不是被我说中了
What did I tell you, huh?
这些俄国佬已经举旗投降了
Russians are waving the white flag already.
你应该知道林肯的结局吧
You do know what happened to Lincoln in the end, right?
你逗我呢  光是那部电影的片头就无聊死我了
You kidding? I could barely get through the opening credits.
你知道有考试吧
You knew you had a test?
是的  但是我被锁在...
Yes, but I got locked out of my--
-还是期中考  -是的  我知道
- A midterm? - Mm, yeah, yeah.
我只不过迟到几分钟
I was only a few minutes late.
而你也知道期中考开始的时间吧
And you knew what time the midterm was scheduled to begin?
是的
Yeah.
但你却没能准时到场
Yet you weren't there on time.
这不是明摆着的事吗
I think that's been established.
而其他人都到了
And everyone else was?
我不清楚  没有仔细点人数
I don't know. I didn't count heads.
我只想要一次考试的机会
Look, I just want a chance to take the test, okay?
你们可以先扣我十分  怎么都行
You can take ten points off, whatever you have to do.
考试迟到真的不是我的错
It really wasn't my fault that I was late, okay?
人有时就是倒霉  不是吗
I mean, stuff just happens sometimes, right?
比方说  要是有个学生急需心肺复苏
Okay, listen, you know, what if a student needed C.P.R.
或者是噎住了  我总不能见死不救吧
Or was choking, and I stopped to save his life?
真要那样又怎么办
I mean, what then?
与其花心思在假想中的濒死学生身上
Well, instead of some hypothetical dying student,
我们不妨来考虑下真实的学生吧
I'd suggest we consider a live one--
杰·桑托斯
Jay Santos.
谁
Who?
没能获得让你付得起这所大学学费的
Runner-up for the glind scholarship you received
奖学金的落选者
that allowed you to attend this university.
我不知道他人现在在哪
I don't know where Jay Santos is,
但如果他在这里  有一件事我能确定
but if he were here, I'm sure of one thing.
他一定会准时参加期中考试
He would have been on time for his midterm.
就当自己长了个教训吧  菲利普
Think of this as a learning experience, Philip.
天有不测风云  所以我们才会未雨绸缪
Things do happen, so we have to anticipate that they might.
我相信下次考试时  你一定会留出时间
I'm sure next test, you'll leave plenty of extra time
早早到场
and arrive early.
这边
Come on!
萨莎
Sasha.
等会  你就是萨莎
Wait. You're Sasha?
你比我想象中个子小多了
You are smaller than I thought you would be, hmm.
彼此彼此
Ditto.
从现在起接干逼涨两成  口交涨三成
Okay, look, it's 20% raise on bumping uglies, 30% on B.Js.
而且不能搞浣肠脱粪这种变态玩法
And whatever happens in the ass stays in the ass.
我不明白你的意思
I don't know what that means.
就是说额外服务是妓女们收钱  而不是你
That means the lady's pocket tips for extras, not you.
嘴挺硬的
Huh, you a tough negotiator?
你需要姑娘们
You need girls.
一点不错
True.
她们在切尔诺贝利周边长大  进价打折
They grew up near Chernobyl, so I got a discount.
价格还可以商量
I'm flexible on those numbers.
你拉走的那几个都快被玩烂了
Your girls are tired and stretched out.
去你妈的
Go fuck yourself.
生日就快到了
Big birthday coming up.
你还记得
You remembered.
毕竟你把这事记在我的日历里了
Well, you put it in my calendar--
字写得超大  双下划线
Huge letters, double underline.
你想怎么庆祝
What do you want to do to celebrate?
我想今年还是低调点吧
I was thinking of low-keying it this year.
不是吧  三十大寿就这么过
Really? For the big 3-0?
混蛋
Asshole.
难不成是四十大寿
4-0?
男朋友说这种话
Said the boyfriend
显然是这辈子都不想再滚床单了
who apparently never wants to get laid again.
他来这里干嘛
What's he doing here?
还能有什么事  他只不过是在
What else? He's putting
-将他最伟大的才能应用于实践  -也就是
- his greatest talent to work. - Which is?
从我爸那变着法地套钱
Weaseling money out of my dad.
那么  关于生日
So, birthday.
穿内裤了吗
抱歉  你说什么
Sorry. What?
我大可穿条丁字裤从蛋糕里跳出来
I mean, I could jump out of a cake in nothing but a thong.
-把内裤脱了  -别再发了
抱歉
Sorry.
我...  家里孩子发过来的
I-it's one of the kids.
没事吧
Everything okay?
没事  我只是...
Yeah, I just--
怎么  下面湿了吗
这样  你先把
Here, I'll let you deal
家里的事处理妥当了
with whatever's going down at Chez Gallagher.
生日想好怎么过告诉我一声
You just let me know what you want to do on your big day,
我们一起来实现
and we'll make it happen. All right.
进来吧  我们到了  各位
Get in here. Here we go, guys.
这些人是谁
Who are they?
跟你说了  我出去办事了
I told you, I had to run an errand.
这就是你在家得宝买到的东西
This is what you picked up at Home Depot?
米奇其实是个明白人
Mickey's not as dumb as he looks.
这些非法移民想工作想到疯
Illegals are desperate for work,
几块钱对他们来说都算是赚大发了
and a few bucks is a fortune for these guys.
这是双赢的策略
It's a win-win.
你叫什么来着  名字
Hey, what's your name again? Uh, nombre?
我的名字吗  帕科
Mi nombre? Paco.
帕科  到柜台后面去
Paco, get behind the bar.
找根拖把开始拖地
Grab a mop, okay?
你俩跟我来
You two come with me.
知道石棉是什么吗
You guys know what asbestos is?
很好  过来
Good. Come on.
叫她们赶紧闭嘴
Tell them to shut the fuck up!
-你害得她们失业了  -是的  我知道
- You take jobs away! - Yes, I know!
我会想出办法的
And I will think of something!
她们说你他妈就是个臭傻逼
They say you are stupid, fucking idiot!
-你怎么回应的  -说你的鸡巴小得可怜
- Well, what did you say back? - That you also have small dick.
我操  不都说男人的家庭
Jesus Christ, what happened to a man's home
是他的坚强后盾吗
being his fucking castle?
三件事  一  这是我的家
Three things--this is my home.
二  你的鸡巴确实小
You do have a small dick.
三  这事是你自找的  谁叫你总把
And you started this, all because you thought
你老婆的逼看得那么金贵呢
your wife's worth more than a couple of bucks a lay.
过来人奉劝一句  她不值那个价
Let me tell you from experience--she's not.
我听不懂你他妈在说什么
I don't know what the fuck you're saying!
我的天
Oh, my god!
我不知道那是什么意思
I don't know what that means.
别担心
Look, don't worry!
我们会尽快找人嫖你们的  奶奶的
We'll get a dick in you as soon as we can. Fuck.
曼迪在家吗
Is Mandy home?
爸
Dad?
你看到我的止痛药了吗  我到处找都找不到
You seen my happy pills? I can't find them anywhere.
看我弄到什么了
Look what I got.
《警网铁金刚》
Bullitt?
我趁收银员在后面抽大麻的时候
I stole it from the store
从店里顺手偷的
while the checkout guy was huffing out back.
你说过  这是你最喜欢的片子
You said it was your favorite.
电影卖座的两大黄金法则
Two keys to cinematic gold--
史蒂夫·麦奎因加大批好车
Steve McQueen and fast cars.
人们都说我年轻的时候跟他挺像
You know, people said I resembled him as a young man.
躺好了  我去给你热点汤
Get comfortable. I heated you up some soup.
你真会照顾你老爸
You really know how to take care of your old man.
谢谢你  儿子
Thank you, son.
卡尔  你干什么呢
Carl. What you doing?
快好了  我杀蟑螂罢了
Almost ready. Just killing a roach.
蟑螂真大呀
Big fucking roach.
他人很好  而且我真的很喜欢他
He's so nice, and-- and I really like him.
我觉得是时候更进一步了
I think it's time we take it to the next level.
你现在多大了
How old are you now?
-十三岁  -那你还等什么
- 13. - What took you so long?
所以我才来找你  你懂我的意思
This is why I came to you. You get it.
菲奥娜总想让我做个长不大的小姑娘
Fiona wants me to stay a little girl forever.
那你怎么还没行动
So what's stopping you?
他说他还没准备好  这是什么意思
He said he wasn't ready. What does that mean?
-他比你大吗  -是  他二十了
- He's older? - Mm-hmm, he's 20.
-真厉害  -谢谢
- Wow. - Thanks.
他只是不想惹上麻烦罢了
He just doesn't want to get in trouble.
他要先确定你是完全自愿
He needs to know that you're totally cool with it
并且事后不会去报警
and won't go running to the cops afterwards.
-报警干嘛  -告他嫖宿幼女
- The cops? - Statutory rape.
一些从女人穿紧身衣
Some old-school shit left over
而且不带防狼喷雾的时候流传下来的陈词滥调
from when women wore corsets and didn't carry mace.
确定你准备好了吗
Sure you're ready?
-那就让他知道  -怎么做
- So let him know. - But how?
宝贝  我走了
Hey, babe, I'm out.
看着
Watch.
又来  我要迟到了
Again? I'm gonna be late for work.
别这样  宝贝
Oh, come on, girl.
行了  我觉得我做不出来
It's okay. I don't think I'd be able to do that.
那就给他发张自拍
So just send him a selfie.
自拍
A selfie?
就是照片
You know, a picture.
好吧
Okay.
你以为你在干什么
What do you think you're doing?
在做拉面  要来点吗
Making ramen. Want some?
我告诉过你不要再给我发短信了
I told you to stop texting me.
是吗
Did you?
"不要"两个字
What part of "stop"
有哪不明白吗
do you not understand?
你来这干什么
What are you doing here?
告诉你这个死脑筋我们已经结束了
Trying to get it through your thick skull that this is over.
是吗
Is it?
是啊
Yes.
你可以...
Well, I mean, you could've, uh--
你可以打电话
You could've called...
或者发短信
or texted...
用脸书
used Facebook.
我不玩脸书
I'm not on facebook.
是吗
No?
罗比  是我
Yo, Robbie, it's me.
你知道他要来吗
Did you know he was coming over?
不知道
No.
我听见你在里面的动静了  快点开门
I can hear you moving around in there. Come on, open up.
我的天  你要干什么
Oh, my-- what are you doing?
麦克在敲门
Mike's at the door.
别理他啊
Well, don't answer it!
-罗比  -来了
- Robbie. - Coming!
你就在这附近吗
Were you in the neighborhood?
是啊  抱歉  我应该先打个电话的
Yeah. Sorry. I probably should have called.
没关系
That's all right.
怎么了
What's up?
我想知道  你今天来找爸所为何事
I wanted to know what you went and saw dad about today.
跟你无关
None of your damn business.
你找他要了多少钱  罗比
How much you ask him for, Robbie?
要喝点什么吗  我给你倒一杯
Can I get you a drink? I'm gonna get you a drink.
你知道他给你的钱
You know the money he gives you
都是从我拼了命
comes right out of the company
才盈利的公司里拿的吗
that I bust my ass to make profitable?
这就关我事了
That makes it my business.
我这有瓶红牛  半瓶雪碧
I got a red bull and a half a sprite,
但是我不确定放了多久了
but I can't vouch for how long that's been in there.
爸从他的退休金里
Look, dad takes the money he gives you
取钱给你
out of his retirement account.
我还有水  不过不是什么贵价货
And I got water, but not the fancy kind.
好吧  都行  我随便
All right, yeah, whatever. Whatever's fine, I don't care.
你确定你不要
Well, you know, you sure you just don't want
-去冰箱里看一眼吗  -好吧
- to look in the fridge? - All right, that's fine.
等等  这有一瓶
Oh, wait. I got a bottle.
汽水  我知道你喜欢这个吧
Bubbles. I know what you like, right?
我知道你以为他们很有钱
Listen, I know you think that they're rich,
但是他们没有你想的那么有钱
but they don't have nearly as much as you think they do.
你看起来不错
You look good.
是啊  我男朋友也这么觉得
Yeah, my boyfriend thinks so.
男朋友啊
Boyfriend, huh?
你在这干嘛
What are you doing here?
打个招呼
Just saying hi.
知道吗  我今天在学校砸了一堆车窗
You know I smashed up a bunch of car windows at school today?
用锤子吗
Hammer?
其实是个弯管机
No, it was a pipe bender, actually.
让一帮条子追
Got chased by the cops--
其实是校园保安  这不是重点
Well, campus security, but still.
他们抓到你了吗
They catch you?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
反正  我  我想起你了
Anyway, it, um-- it made me think of you.
肆意搞破坏让你想起了我
Random destruction makes you think of me?
是啊  其实
Yeah, it was, uh...
其实很美的
It was beautiful.
你想干什么
What do you want?
我不知道  我
I don't know. I, um...
我有好几次都差点给你打电话了
I almost called you a couple times.
估摸着你在忙自己的事
I figured you were doing your own thing.
我就是想你了
I just missed you.
你男朋友在吗
Is your boyfriend here?
客厅里那些妞是干嘛的
Who are those chicks in the living room?
-妓女  -妓女
- Hookers. - Hookers?
米奇的老婆  说来话长
Mickey's wife, long story.
我都快忘了这感觉有多好了
You know, I almost forgot how good this feels.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
操
Shit.
抱歉  我也没想到会秒射
Sorry. I didn't mean for that to be a sprint.
你没跟那些联谊会的无聊小妞做过吗
Not getting any from the white-bread sorority sluts?
这不一样
It's not the same.
你身上有现金吗
You got any cash on you?
裤袋里可能有点
Yeah, yeah, there might be something down there.
不好说  在学生会洗盘子
I don't know-- I'm not exactly raking it in
可发不了什么财
bussing dishes at the student union.
我得去买紧急避孕药
Oh, yeah, I need the morning-after pill.
或者不用
Or not.
我好像在排卵  乳房很酸
I think I'm ovulating. My tits are sore.
我应该用个套的
I could have just used one of those condoms.
肯亚塔用的巨无霸尺寸套套
Kenyatta's trojan magnums would have slipped
会直接从你的细小嫩白老二上滑下来的
right off of your skinny, little, white Johnson.
真伤人
Ouch. Harsh.
就六块钱
6 bucks?
那就
So, uh...
别吃药了
Skip the pill.
去你妈的  你知道现在流产多贵吗
Fuck you. You know how much an abortion costs now?
赌一把吧
Oh, roll the dice.
天又不会塌下来
Yeah, it wouldn't be the worst thing in the world--
穷崽子们跑来跑去
Having a little ghetto rug rat running around.
这不好笑
That's not funny.
我认真的
I'm serious.
对  我就需要这个
Yeah, that's just what I need,
我在这个地方养你的崽子
raising your bastard kid in the hood
而你在机器人实验室后面上你的女同学
while you bang co-eds in the back of a robotics lab.
再也没有什么女同学跟机器人实验室了
Not gonna be any co-eds or any robotics lab.
为什么
Why?
那个地方糟透了
Well, the place is bullshit...
我早就说过
just like I said it would be.
-我不干了  -你要退学吗
- I'm bailing. - You're quitting?
你知道我费了多大劲才让你进去的吗
You know how hard I worked to get you in there?
那你去
Then you go.
凭我1.2的绩点  他们可不会要我
I don't think they'd accept my 1.2 GPA.
你不能就这么不干了
You--you can't just bail.
别提了  好吗
Drop it, okay?
是你来找我的  混蛋
You came to me, asshole.
对不起  我觉得糟透了
Look, I'm sorry, all right? I felt like shit.
我是来找乐子的  不是让你审问我
I thought this would be fun, not an interrogation.
所以呢  你感觉糟糕或者想退出了
So what, whenever you feel like shit or want to quit,
就能跳上轻轨来搞大我的肚子吗
you figure you can hop on the EL and come and knock me up?
我错了  不会再这样了
My mistake. It won't happen again.
白痴
Shithead!
贱货
Skank.
我不想做坏人
You know, I hate being the bad guy.
但是你这坏人做得真好
But you're so good at it.
好吧  想想我说的话好吗
All right, think about what I said, yeah?
行了
All right.
谢了
Thanks.
-两次  -真的假的  别闹
- Oh. Twice. - Serious? Come on.
-好了  -再见
- All right.  - Later.
你个贱人
You're a motherfucker.
要继续吗
Want to pick up where we left off?
-你有病吧  -不是我叫他来的
- What is wrong with you? - I didn't ask him to come over.
而且  你跟我一样爽
Plus, you got off on it as much as I did.
你说什么
Excuse me?
物以类聚
Game recognizes game.
我们不是一类
We are nothing alike.
等下
Hold on.
你介意我接个电话吗  是我女朋友
Oh, you mind if I take this? It's my girlfriend.
以后离我远点
Don't ever come near me again.
你他妈对我干嘛了
What the fuck did you do to me?
我救了你的命
I saved your life.
过来
上帝啊
Jesus!
准备好了吗
Ready?
等下  等下
Wait, wait, wait.
行了
Okay.
操
Oh, fuck.
神啊
Oh, God.
救命
Help!
救命  谁来救救他
Help! Someone, please, help!
我爸摔倒了  起不来了
My dad's fallen, and he can't get up!
-天啊  -他受伤了
- Oh, my God. - He's hurt!
快来救救他
Please, help!
没关系
No, it's okay.
没事  弄出去就行了
It's okay. Just get it out.
弄走
Get it out.
伙计
Hey, man.
什么风把你吹来了  利普
Look who it is-- Lip!
过得怎么样  伙计
How you doing, man?
从象牙塔远道而来啊
Straight from the ivory tower.
黑眼圈不错
Nice shiner.
因为太聪明被教授揍了一顿吗
What, a professor clock you for being a smart-ass?
不不  跟人打了一架  我想喝杯啤酒
No, no, I got in a fight. I-I could use a beer.
好  再来个冰袋  先坐吧
Yeah, yeah, and an ice pack. Take a seat.
门没关
Oh, the door's open.
-我马上出来  -好的
- I'll be out in a sec. - Okay.
你来了
Hey, you.
怎么样
How you doing?
黛比  黛比  黛比
Ooh, Debbie, Debbie, Debbie.
黛比  黛比  停  停下
Debbie, Debbie, stop, stop.
我哪做得不对吗
Uh, am I not doing it right?
不是  你这是怎么了
No, what-- what has gotten into you?
我...  你怎么反倒问起我了
I--why did you ask me over?
我以为你喜欢我发的照片呢
I thought you liked the picture I sent.
我删掉了
I-I mean, I deleted it.
为什么
Well, why?
黛比  你很好
Debbie, you're awesome.
跟你在一起很快乐
I mean, I have a great time with you.
-只是...  -不不  没关系
- It's just-- - No, no, it's okay.
我不会去报警或是怎样的
I'm not gonna run to the cops or anything.
这不关警察的事
This isn't about the cops.
或许有点吧  但主要是因为你
I mean, maybe a little, but it's you.
不是  我嘴笨
No. That came out wrong.
难道你不想要吗
Don't you want to?
想  将来某一天
Sure, yeah. Yeah, someday.
为什么不是现在
Why not now?
因为你才13岁
'Cause you're 13.
然后呢
So?
你太小了
You're just too young.
我不小了  我准备好了
I'm not a little girl. I'm ready.
我知道你觉得自己不小了
I know--I know you think you are...
但是...
But...
黛比
Debbie.
小黛  别  别走
Deb, no. Please, stay.
小黛
Deb!
每年花五万块
It's 50 grand a year
换来四年的兄弟会派对
for four years of frat parties, you know,
一帮高智商怪胎  还要速读三百年前的小说
intellectual circle jerks, speed reading 300-year-old novels
结果考完试就忘得一干二净
that'll be forgotten the second the test is over,
就因为别人告诉我们在这个世界上
All because, you know, we're told we can't succeed
缺了这张文凭我们就会一事无成
in the world without a piece of paper.
一派胡言
You know, and it's bullshit.
比尔·盖茨退学了
Bill Gates dropped out.
对吧  还有史蒂夫·乔布斯
All right. Steve Jobs.
黑鹰队就是那儿中央分区的吗
That's that center for the blackhawks?
大学就是个大骗局
Yeah, you know, it's just all one big collegiate scam.
很高兴那种地方没有把你变成二逼精英
Well, I'm glad that place didn't turn you into an elitist prick.
没有  我还是跟你们一样的南区屌丝
No, I'm still a south side prick like all the rest of you.
老天爷  俄罗斯婊子们不给人吹箫时
Jesus Christ, Russian whores know how to run their mouths
嘴巴倒活动得挺勤快
when there ain't some dude's junk jammed in there.
你不是在上大学还是什么的吗
Aren't you supposed to be at college or some shit?
没有  跟康德和米尔顿·弗里德曼说拜拜了
Nope. Packing up my kant and milton friedman.
我受够那些扯屁了
I'm done with all that crap.
你一开始为什么要去他家
Why'd you go over there in the first place?
-告诉他一切都结束了  -可以打电话啊
- To tell him to knock it off. - Could've called.
-你还帮他说话  -得了吧
- You're taking his side? - Please.
你就想被上  你这个小荡妇
You wanted a hit, you little smackhead.
不是的
I did not.
是吗  你走到他门前的时候
Really? Did you get that little tingle
你心里就没有一丁点激动吗
when you stepped up to his front door?
或许吧
Maybe.
你想让我说什么  说我有自毁倾向
What do you want me to say, that--that I'm self-destructive,
说我看到骗子  小偷和瘾君子就把持不住吗
that--that liars and thieves and addicts turn me on,
还是说我不知道如何正常恋爱
that--that I don't know how to do a normal relationship?
有这么难吗
Was that so hard?
最糟的一点
The worst part...
是我不停地看他有没有发短信过来
is I keep checking my phone to see if he's texted.
我他妈究竟是怎么了
I mean, what the fuck is wrong with me?
谁他娘的把我药柜砸了
Who the hell broke into my pills?
你刚说不回学校了是开玩笑的吧
You were joking, right, about not going back to college?
不  认真的  我受够了
Nope. Serious, I'm done.
我还以为你只是闹脾气
I was hoping you were just blowing off some steam.
事实上  这也不全由我说了算
The truth is, it's not only up to me, all right?
我成绩很差
My grades suck.
我回去的唯一可能就是
But the only reason I'm going back there
收拾东西  然后离开
is to pack my shit and split.
那你退学后怎么办呢
So you quit. Then what?
我会想办法的
I'll figure it out.
怎么了
What?
成熟点吧
Grow a pair.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你听见了  坚强点  伙计
You heard me. Tough it out, man.
你是个娘们吗
What are you, a pussy?
我已经说过了  不是我说了算的
It--it's like I said. It's not only up to me.
你鬼主意那么多  会想到办法的
You're resourceful. You'll figure it out.
小凯  这是从我离家去上大学以后
Look, Kev, this is the first good day I've had
第一个高兴的日子
since I left for that shithole.
利普  难道你想跟我一样
Lip, do you-- do you want to end up like me...
钱一分一分扣着花
clawing for every penny,
祈祷能想到办法养活家人吗
praying that you can figure out some way to support your family?
我现在就是这状态
'Cause that's what I'm going through.
欠了一屁股债
I got bills up to my ass.
我告诉你  这日子糟透了
Let me tell you something, it fucking sucks.
你鬼主意那么多  会想到办法的
Well, you're resourceful. You'll figure it out.
大学就是个骗局  是吧
College is a racket, huh?
你想想看
Well, guess what.
没人比你更擅长钻体制的漏洞了
There's no one better at beating the system than you.
你可以让他们免费给你上四年大学
Hell, man, you got them to give you four fucking years for free.
为什么不能拿到学位
Why don't you get your damn diploma,
唾他们一脸  走出自己的大好前程
spit in their faces, and have a fucking future?
小凯  我只是想喝点小酒
Kev, I am just trying to drink my beer,
享受回家的感觉
enjoy being back home.
这不是你家  这是你长大的地方
This isn't your home. It's where you grew up.
你不属于这里
It's not where you're supposed to be.
怎么  你还能裁定
And what, now you're the arbiter
谁属于哪里了
on where everybody's supposed to be?
可能吧  如果我知道"裁定"意思的话
Yeah, maybe, if I knew what "arbiter" meant.
我受够了别人告诉我
You know, I'm getting pretty damn tired of everybody
该去哪里  该做什么了
telling me where I should be and what I should be doing.
那就别给他们机会说啊
Well, then stop making them have to.
他妈的成熟起来
Grow the fuck up!
-谢谢你的啤酒  -不客气
- Thanks for the beers, Kev. - Yeah, you're welcome.
-操你自己  -打飞机挺爽的
- G.F.Y. - Yeah, T.G.I.F.
霍莉在吗
Is Holly here?
她不接电话
She's not answering her phone.
他跟一个戴鼻环的家伙走了
She left with some guy, had a nose ring.
那家伙就跟胜利的公牛似的
Made him look like a prize bull.
你想去别处玩玩吗
You want to go somewhere?
去哪
Where?
厕所  跟我一起
The bathroom, with me.
去不去
Yes or no?
去
Okay.
好了  儿子  我自己来吧
Okay, son, I can take it from here.
走  快走
Go. Vamonos.
待会见
Hasta luego.
我靠  别
Oh, fuck! Don't--
弗兰克
Frank?
是我
It's just me.
进来吧
Come on.
-关灯还是开灯  -关了吧
- Lights on or off? - Off, please.
你以前这样做过吗
So have you done this before?
做过
Yeah.
我也做过
Me too.
那么
So, uh,
你想怎么做
how do you want to do it?
你以前是怎么做的
Um, however you've done it before.
好吧
Okay.
或者可以照你以前那样做
Or we could do it how you've done it before.
我现在把衣服脱掉
I'm gonna take my shirt off now.
好
Cool.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我做不来
I can't do this.
没关系
That's okay.
我好像已经射了
I think I already did.
抱歉在你测试完了以后没能去接你
Sorry I didn't come get you after your tests, but...
遇到事故了
I had the accident.
之后没见到你
When you never came back,
还以为你跟以前
I thought maybe you'd turned out
我遇过的那些臭男人一样呢
to be like all the other men in my life.
绝不可能
Not a chance.
疼吗
How's the pain?
还行  现在有你在身边
It's okay... Now that I'm here with you.
他们安排手术了吗
Did they schedule the transplant?
保险公司的
I'll have the money
赔偿支票一到我就有钱了
as soon as Liberty Mutual cuts the check.
有一个好消息和一个坏消息
Um, good news and bad news.
先听好的
Okay, good?
我把恰奇送到邻居家了
I sent Chuckie to the neighbor's
所以今晚不会有人打扰我们
so we can be alone tonight.
棒极了
Great.
那坏消息是什么
Uh, what's the bad?
我们不匹配
We're not a match.
什么
What?
管移植手术的女士说
The transplant lady said
我的白细胞会攻击你的白细胞
my white blood cells attacked yours.
它们为什么要攻击我的
Why the fuck did they do that?
我也不知道
Oh, I-I don't know.
-我很抱歉  -抱歉
- I'm so sorry. - Sorry?
那对我有什么用
What the hell does-- good does that do me?
我要的是肝  不是道歉
I need a liver, not a goddamn apology!
弗兰克
Frank--
你知道我都经历了些什么吗
Do you know what I've been through?
我把腿摔断了
I shattered my leg in six places!
酒也戒了
I stopped drinking!
我知道你很沮丧  但我们...
I know you're disappointed, but we're--
我只求一小片肝
Just one small piece of liver.
就够了  但是不行
That's all I need, but, no!
谢谢你了  上帝
Thank you, god!
谢谢你这滑稽可笑的拒绝
Thank you for the cosmic "fuck you."
竟然跟自己的女儿都不匹配
Even my own daughter isn't a match!
什么
W-what?
还想怎么折磨我
Anything else you want to throw at me?
要不来点嗜肉性病毒怎么样
How about a flesh-eating virus, huh?
想给我来点吗
Want to toss that in?
你说什么
W-what did you say?
什么
What?
你女儿
Your daughter?
我没说
I-I didn't say that.
你说了
Yes, you did.
没有... 算了
No, I--oh, fuck it!
还有什么关系
What's the use?
现在恨我  以后再恨我
Hate me now, hate me later,
迟早你都会恨我的  到底为什么
You all hate me eventually, and for what?
我又没对你怎么样
What did I ever do to you?
你是我爸爸
You're my dad?
我差点就给你口交了
I almost put you in my mouth.
可不是我要求的
I didn't ask you to do that.
你昨天干蹭了我半小时
You dry-humped my thigh for half an hour yesterday.
干蹭又不算乱伦
Dry-humping is not incest.
天...
Je--
出去
Get out.
你喊什么  我才是没得到肝的人
What are you yelling about? I'm the one not getting a liver.
滚出去
Get out!
老天上帝呀  好吧
Jesus. God almighty. Okay.
-滚  -好好
- Get out! - Okay, okay.
-马上  -知道了  知道了
- Now! - Okay, okay, okay.
-快滚  -好  在滚了
- Now! - Okay, I'm going.
-滚啊  -滚着呢
- Now! - I'm going.
真是每况日下
Every time it gets goddamn worse!
臭变态
Fucking sick!
别再进来
And stay out!
完工了
Terminamos.
全清理干净了吗
You guys all done?
好极了
Oh, muy bien.
那些石棉丢哪了
Where did you dump the asbestos?
算了  还是别告诉我
You know what? You know what? Don't tell me.
我还是不知道得好
It's better that I don't know.
发工资了
Huh? Here you go.
每人一张
One for each of you.
别都寄回家了
Don't send it all back home, okay?
谢啦  各位朋友
Thanks, amigos.
帕科  给我的朋友们每人半杯烈酒
Hey, Paco, get a round of half shots for my friends here.
只有半杯哦
Make sure it's half shots, okay?
-小凯  -什么事
- Yo, Kev. - Yeah?
楼上公寓清理干净了吗
You clean out that apartment yet?
刚刚弄干净
Yeah, yeah, I just got it cleaned out.
准备发些传单
I'm gonna set up some flyers
看看能不能租出去
and see if I can rent it out.
我有办法让你赚更多
I know how you can make a boatload more.
按小时出租
Rent it by the hour.
婊子我有了
Look, I got the labor force already.
只欠客源和一个场所
All I need is clientele and a location.
这两样你都有
You got both.
黛比
Debbie?
你怎么了
What's going on?
你没事吧
Hey, you okay?
怎么了  来开开门
What's going on? Come on, open up.
跟我聊聊
Talk to me, please.
你怎么了
What's going on?
我男朋友...
My boyfriend...
我搞砸了
I messed up.
怎么回事
How?
你搞砸了
You screwed up.
证明了你是加拉格家的孩子
That just proves you're a Gallagher.
让我告诉你一个秘密
Let me let you in on a little secret.
我也不知道自己到底在干嘛
I don't know what the hell I'm doing either.
那个谁不知道
Who doesn't know that?
我只是希望自己能
I just wish I could skip the part
跳过彷徨无措  直接到达
where I don't know the right thing to do
看透明了的阶段
and get to the part where I do.
我也是
Me too.
谢了
Thank you.
来杯水
Water.
全是为了我的肝  朋友
My kingdom for a lobe, amigo.
全是为了我的肝
My kingdom for a lobe.
没想到会再见到你
I didn't expect to see you again.
你知道我有多少次在夜里睡不着
Do you know how many nights I laid awake,
年复一年
year after year...
好奇你在哪里
wondering where you were,
不知道你有没有想起过我
if you ever thought about me?
你有吗
Did you...
这么久以来
Ever?
没有
No.
但现在会了
I will now, though.
我很抱歉没早点告诉你
I'm sorry. I should've told you sooner.
我只是不想毁了我们的关系
I-I just didn't want to ruin what we had together.
来吧  请我喝杯啤酒
Come on, buy me a fucking beer.
我要给我女儿点一杯啤酒
I need a beer for my daughter here.
我想补考
I want a retest.
你在这里等了多久
How long have you been out here?
几个小时吧  不想错过你
Uh, a couple hours. I didn't want to miss you.
你要是昨天考试的时候
I wish you'd shown this concern
能这么在乎时间就好了
for punctuality yesterday.
这就是你的目标吗
Is that your goal,
教出一批守时的学生
to graduate students who can punch a clock?
我的目标是教出可以处理
My goal is to graduate students who can manage
来自真实世界各种要求的学生
the organizational demands of the real world.
明白  听着
Okay, listen, listen.
我明白那些真实世界的各种要求
I understand all of the demands of the real world, okay?
只是这个地方的各种要求
It's just the demands of this place
我还没完全弄清楚
that are taking me some time to figure out.
但是就快弄清楚了
But I'm--I'm getting there.
我只是需要有个人跟我说  "没关系"
I just need someone to say, "fuck it",
行吗  "这孩子受的苦够多了"
all right? "This kid deserves a break."
那人就是我了吧
I take it that's me?
-测验簿带了吗  -带了
- You got a blue book? - Yeah.
就在这
Right here.
笔呢
Pen?
带了三支  以防万一
Yeah, I got three, just in case.
那么  没关系了
Then fuck it.
这是高中毕业照
That's my high-school graduation.
发型挺酷的
Nice mullet.
第一次婚礼
Oh, first wedding.
要是当时我在你身边  送你走到圣坛该多好
I wish I could've been there to walk you down the aisle.
你现在在我身边了
You're here now.
请忽略
Ignore that.